<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_url">https://droidterm-e8a40.firebaseapp.com/droidvim</string>
    <string name="help_git">https://droidterm-e8a40.firebaseapp.com/droidvim/index.html#git-libpath</string>

    <string name="summary_color_preference">After changing the terminal color, we recommended restart this app.</string>
    <string name="summary_ambiwidth_preference">Treat Ambiguous Characters as full width character for East Asian fonts. (:help ambiwidth)</string>
    <string name="summary_home_dir_chooser_preference">`.vimrc` and `.vim` are read from `$HOME` (Restart required)</string>
    <string name="choose_home_directory_message">HOME directory:\nChanging the HOME directory is not recommended. Use Startup Directory.\n\nIf you change the HOME directory, you will not be able to change the attributes of the file.\nYou can restore the home directory to the default value by pressing \"Default\" button.\n\nviminfo:\nSince viminfo requires an attribute change, please add `set viminfo+=n$APPFILES/home/.viminfo` to .vimrc.</string>

    <string name="tips_vim">How to quit:\n- Type \":qa\".\n- Double tap -> \"QUIT\".\n\nToggle keyboard:\n- Double tap near the bottom of the screen\n- Back button\n\nDirect input:\n- If you need to enable word suggestions or to input Non-Alphanumeric characters, tap \"◇\" button on function bar. \n- One-line text box can be turned on/off by \"Double tap near the right edge of the screen\".\n\nVim tutorial:\n- Tap \"Vim tutorial\" from the long press menu or type \":Vimtutor\".</string>
    <string name="tips_vim_list">.vim and .vimrc:\n\n`$HOME` is deleted when uninstalling. So we recommended copy `.vim` and `.vimrc` to internal storage (It can be accessed via filer app) and edit .vimrc via long press menu.\n\t HTML and Links:\n \n Open the HTML file in the browser.\n - \"Menu\" -> \"Share\" -> \"File\"\n - `:ShareIntent file`\n \n gx - open URL under the cursor (:h gx)\t Clipboard commands\n\n Vim command:\n - \"*p - Paste from the clipboard.\n - \"*yy - Copy to the clipboard.\n \n Only on DroidVim:\n - gY - unnamed register to the clipboard (e.g. yygY)\n - \"Menu\"->\"Share\"\t By default direct input is forced, so you may not be able to input your (Non-English)language.\nIn that case please try the following:\n\n- ◇ Button\n- One-line text box\n- IME shortcuts(physical keyboard)\n- Change \"Input mode at startup\" to \"Normal input\"\t Keep screen:\n\nTemporarily change the time to sleep.\n - \"Menu\"->\"Screen\"->"Keep screen" \tYou can change the text input mode from Vim script.\nSee \"Help\"->\"Tips\"\t External SD card\n- To read/write an external SD card, choose \"Storage\" → \"3 dot menu\" → \"Show SD card\".\tYou can use a 256 terminal color scheme.\nTry `:colorscheme term256`\tFunction bar cursor button direction:\n - Synchronize with the state of the Ctrl button. ESC button to quit.\tSwipe the bottom half of the screen left and right to move the cursor.</string>
</resources>
